bestmediainfo.com 2010-12-28

# Privacy Policy « Best Media Info, News and Analysis on Indian Advertising, Marketing and Media Industry.

[Home](http://www.bestmediainfo.com/ "Go to Home.") > Privacy Policy 

## Privacy Policy

 **[www.BestMediaInfo.com](http://www.bestmediainfo.com/) is maintained by:** **Best Media Info**

A-27L, Sector-16, Noida  
Uttar Pradesh, India – 201301 Ph.: +91 120 4359565.  
We can be reached by e-mail at [Info@BestMediaInfo.com.](mailto:Info@BestMediaInfo.com?subject=News%20Releases)

BestMediaInfo has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: [www.BestMediaInfo.com](http://www.bestmediainfo.com/).

Any personal information identifying any visitor to the [www.BestMediaInfo.com](http://www.bestmediainfo.com/) or Subscriber (“Personal Information”) if required, is asked for explicitly in the relevant page on the portal. Personal Information is used to operate the [www.BestMediaInfo.com](http://www.bestmediainfo.com/), and we may occasionally inform you of new features, services, and products from the Company.

If at any time you believe the [www.BestMediaInfo.com](http://www.bestmediainfo.com/) has not adhered to these principles, please notify us by e-mail to Info@BestMediaInfo.com and we will use all commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and correct the problem.

If you have questions about this policy, please e-mail us at [Info@BestMediaInfo.com.](mailto:Info@BestMediaInfo.com?subject=News%20Releases)

BestMediaInfo site’s registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). The customer’s contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor the visitor’s experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.

This site contains links to other sites. [www.BestMediaInfo.com](http://www.bestmediainfo.com/) is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

BestMediaInfo’s online surveys ask visitors for contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). We use contact data from our surveys to send the user information about our company. The customer’s contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor’s experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.

We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). We use contact data from our contests to send users information about our company. The customer’s contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor’s experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. ****

**Choice/Opt-Out**

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.

  1. You can send email to Info@BestMediaInfo.com
  2. You may unsubscribe our email services by clicking unsubscribe link given on our all kind of emails.

**Correct/Update** This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided.

  1. You can send email to Info@BestMediaInfo.com
  2. You may re-subscribe to our services after making the required changes. Please **[click here](http://www.bestmediainfo.com/Homepage/Register.aspx)** to register again.

**Contacting the Web Site** If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Website, you can contact [Info@BestMediaInfo.com.](mailto:Info@BestMediaInfo.com?subject=News%20Releases)
